[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "Do you condemn them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Absolute tragedy, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Would you condemn them for calling for those protests?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "I think unfortunately it's going to put more fuel on the fire that was already lit today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Terry Jones"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Where will this end, do you think, Corey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, think all too often extremists on both sides, the violent extremists that did the attack today, the extremists down in Florida, Terry Jones, control this conversation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Corey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What is the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, the government is the government here is dismissing out of hand, it seems, the conditional cease-fire that the opposition has put forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Is that accurate, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "He feels he has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Are they going to continue them at the level they have been at, serious and aggressive, or are they going to start to back off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Nic, thank you very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Yemen"], "PERSON": ["Saleh"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "How long has he got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, Piers, if you talk to government officials like we've been doing in Yemen, many have already written the President Saleh's political obituary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Would you blame Mr. Jones for what happened today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I think what he did was certainly unnecessary and I think the consequences have been horrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "I mean, there's got to be some way of stopping people like Terry Jones behaving this way, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, certainly, you want him not to do things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Terry Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "NATO", "Arab League"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Is it a sensible time for America to be withdrawing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Well, honestly, Piers, I do think that it is time for the other countries in NATO and the Arab League to take more charge here, to take more responsibility.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Give me a ballpark.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Why don't you just give them some money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, I don't know that one has anything to do with the other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Will you carry on shooting elephants then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, I will not carry on shooting elephants.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GoDaddy"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, ever since this oafish violent video posted, we have taken our business with GoDaddy and gone elsewhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I disagree with that totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "If you were doing for this some kind of humanitarian purpose, why are you looking like you're some kind of super hunter with your kill there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Let me tell you about the smile I have on my face at that time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "And any other animals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "He's killed other wild animals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Have you had any financial damage to your company, GoDaddy.com, so far, in light this incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "No, none at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["GoDaddy.com"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", ":", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", ":", "JJS", "NNPS", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "So, nobody's removed any money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "And I'll tell you why -- because most people -- most Americans understand people need to eat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Do I seem dangerous to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "You seem relatively harmless, but all the best serial killers are harmless to look at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Where are your limits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "ILVERMAN: I just go by a guideline of -- if it makes my heart sink or it makes me feel bad, then I won't say it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "But don't all comedians want attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "To hang out with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Of course!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Why wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "No, you're a lot of fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "What are you fears?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Oh, my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "What should we talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Rather.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "I mean, what do you want?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I would love to make you cry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "You want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "But only if it helps you, ultimately, if it is some sort of breakthrough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "You're quite bolshy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Are you playful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Or is it like an undercurrent of menace?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "It depends on the situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 374, "question": "How you feeling at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Right now, I'm feeling --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Hamm"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "No, he's an actor named John Hamm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "The types who are in these shows are fairly ghastly, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Right, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "What are you looking at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "I understood that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "That's what I hear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "You hear doit-doit-doit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "It's all the same, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "It's all the same, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Touche.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Is that a British word?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Touche is a French word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Oh, because France is basically Britain, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["France", "Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Across the pond?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Doit, doit, doit, doit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "What your view of your great country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I love America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "You think America loves you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "That is such a weird question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Do you think America loves you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I shouldn't think so for a moment, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 482, "question": "They probably think who is obnoxious little Limey Brit we have got sitting here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I think when you talk about a whole people, it's--", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "How about the great Larry King?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "--getting, you are generalizing a bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry King"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "No, I mean, does it matter to you that you are popular in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I'm popular for a Jew.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Uh, is it not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "I mean, I think when stuff like Mel Gibson, when he said, like, you know, like Jewish stuff or anything like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "But there is outrage when he said things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mel Gibson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "And beautiful and perfect, and it would be true, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "You were very candid in that book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Can you be a successful, smart comedian, without having gone through a lot of crap in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I don't know!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Because your family was-it wasn't a misery scenario was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "No, I mean, you know-yeah, no!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Was it the divorce do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Because what did I have to loose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "ORGAN: From the most unlikely background.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Is that what you felt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "I had nothing to loose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "What would you like from your life that you don't have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Uh, nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "You have an allergy to non-funny people, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "They don't have to be comedians but they have to be funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Do you prefer men that make you laugh, or who laugh at your jokes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Oooh, I think that make me laugh, but both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "You are such weird people, aren't you, comedians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "ILVERMAN: So weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "You know what I mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "We're talking to people who make responsibility for other people's happiness.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Oy!?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Do you still feel as passionate about him as you did then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Yeah!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "You mother (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``"], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Can we fast forward to the bit where you make a complete ass of yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Ugh!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Didn't you then inform him that in your next movie you were going to be nude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "There is-ugh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Can we just have the exact wording?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Well, he goes, \"Well, what's next for you?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "JJ"], "qSentId": 670, "question": "What did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "He defused the situation, you know, generously like-", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "He didn't say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "He said it not in a pervy way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "PRP$", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "What other way can it not be pervy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "But in a let's make her not feel weird by saying a weird thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "The president of the United States immediately responded by asking if you could send him a copy of the movie in which you are naked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "It was levity.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Were you flattered that the president wanted to see you naked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Well, no, because I know what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Michelle was in hearing distance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "And standout, where you walk out, it's live, it's all whatever you want to do, and then it's all over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "They're completely different.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "It is one of those botched names, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "What is your middle name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "Kate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "I wish I could say it's been a pleasure, but it's been tense, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Give me a break.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Should nobody be searched?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "I'm saying only me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Why just you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "Because of who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "You believe in profiling, basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110401pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "Would you only profile Muslims at airports?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]